<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
 <comment>Game mode description language file - Default English</comment>
 <entry key="Marathon">Standard game mode for beginners.</entry>
 <entry key="MarathonPlus">Standard game mode for Various Players. Goal for the "Bonus level"!</entry>
 <entry key="MarathonDrill">How long can you survive against the rising garbage lines?</entry>
 <entry key="MarathonShuttle">Try to empty "GOAL" counter as fast as you can.</entry>
 <entry key="MarathonExtreme">Gameplay is similar to Marathon mode, but it's Much Faster!</entry>
 <entry key="SprintLine">Clear certain number of lines as fast as possible.</entry>
 <entry key="SprintScore">Get certain number of points as fast as possible.</entry>
 <entry key="SprintDig">Clear all garbage lines as fast as possible.</entry>
 <entry key="SprintCombo">Try to clear all the lines in the well in one combo.</entry>
 <entry key="SprintUltra">Score as many points as possible within the time limit.</entry>
 <entry key="MarathonSquare">Create 4x4 squares to get more points.</entry>
 <entry key="RetroN">A classic game that takes you to the nostalgic feeling.</entry>
 <entry key="RetroA">A game based on the classics where efficiency is important.</entry>
 <entry key="RetroS">A classic game that many Japanese players played like a Monkey.</entry>
 <entry key="RetroModern">Modern Arranged RETRO MANIA. What's waiting beyond the level 15...?</entry>
 <entry key="GrandBasic">Try to score many Points and Fireworks as possible, within level 300.</entry>
 <entry key="GrandPuzzle">Erase all gem blocks from the playfield within the time limit.</entry>
 <entry key="GrandM1">Try to score many Points for the better grade,..<reach level 999.</entry>
 <entry key="GrandM2">Grade base is different, and Speed increasing will keep after level 500.</entry>
 <entry key="GrandM3">Each Level Intensity will Vary Greatly by Your Skill!</entry>
 <entry key="GrandM2G">Watch out for rising garbage blocks.</entry>
 <entry key="GrandRoads">Complete Levels by each 10 lines, before runs out the time limit.</entry>
 <entry key="GrandS1">Play High speed Throughout. and Can you break the level 500 barrier?</entry>
 <entry key="GrandS2">Much Faster With Insane Gimmicks. This won't end at level 999 as usual!</entry>
 <entry key="GrandSStealth">This has some speed, and the playfield is gonna invisible!</entry>
 <entry key="GrandZ">Only for players who have INFINITY Brain Power. Good luck!</entry>
 <entry key="Practice">You can practice various speed settings in this mode.</entry>
 <entry key="ToolMapEditor">This is a tool for creating maps for VS-BATTLE mode and NetPlay mode.</entry>
 <entry key="VSBattle">Battle against human or AI opponent.</entry>
 <entry key="VS-SprintLine">Clear certain number of lines before your opponent.</entry>
 <entry key="VS-DIG_RACE">Clear all garbage lines before your opponent.</entry>
 <entry key="Avalanche1P">Connect 4 or more same color blocks to clear them.</entry>
 <entry key="Avalanche1PFever">Premade chains will drop down endlessly.</entry>
 <entry key="AvalancheVS">Clear chains to send your opponent garbage.</entry>
 <entry key="AvalancheVSFever">Use premade chains to attack your opponent.</entry>
 <entry key="AvalancheVSDig">Dig down to the flashing gem before your opponent.</entry>
 <entry key="AvalancheVSBomb">Clear chains to send bombs.</entry>
 <entry key="AvalancheVSSPF">Clear chains to send patterned garbages.</entry>
 <entry key="Physician">Clear gem blocks by lining up blocks of the same color.</entry>
 <entry key="PhysicianVS">Clear all gem blocks before your opponent.</entry>
 <entry key="SPF_VS-BATTLE_lBETAr">Use gems to clear blocks of the same color.</entry>
 <entry key="[MORE...]">You can access more game modes from here.</entry>

 <!--Folder descriptions.-->
 <!--Same rules apply as mode descriptions, but you'll need to add the "_" prefix.-->
 <entry key="_[ALL_MODES]">This folder contains all available game modes.</entry>
 <entry key="_POPULAR_MODES">This folder contains the Recommended modes.</entry>
 <entry key="_Guidelines_Games">TTC Guidelines Based modes. Recommend for beginners!</entry>
 <entry key="_Uniques_Variety">Not-Categorizable variety modes. Have fun the twisted play!</entry>
 <entry key="_Retrospective_style">Nostalgia balanced games. Let's Enjoy the Near-Original!</entry>
 <entry key="_Trial_Rush">In the Simple and Short Race modes, Challenge for your Record!</entry>
 <entry key="_Grand_Challenges">Grade Recognizing modes contained. Try your ability!</entry>
 <entry key="_TYPE_AVALANCHE">Connect 4 or more same color blocks to clear them.</entry>
 <entry key="_TYPE_PHYSICIAN">Clear gem blocks by lining up blocks of the same color.</entry>
 <entry key="_TYPE_SPF">Use gems to clear blocks of the same color.</entry>
</properties>
